# JOAQUIN SOZA GUERRA

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Well-qualified Full Stack Developer familiar with wide range of programming utilities and languages. Knowledgeable of backend and frontend development requirements. Handles any part of process with ease. Collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities offering 4+ years of related experience.

#### WORK HISTORY

# CTO - Blockchain Developer, 07/2023 to Today PaltaLabs - Santiago, Chile

- Currently working as a Blockchain Developer at PaltaLabs (paltalabs.io)
- Building Soroswap (soroswap.finance)

# CTO - Tech Lead - Full Stack Developer, 06/2022 to 06/2023 Rokin - Santiago, Chile

Worked as a Full Stack Developer at Rokin (rokinapp.com), build a wide variety
of solutions from bank scrappers to a variety of integrations (Payment
solutions, brokers, etc)

# Full Stack Developer, 11/2021 to 04/2022 Blockchain DApp - Santiago, Chile

 Worked as a typescript and solidity developer on a blockchain DApp in the Avalanche network (React, Nodejs, Typescript, Solidity, Docker)

## Full Stack Developer /Engineer, 04/2021 to 11/2021 Alpha Spa - Santiago, Chile

 We were a two man team, we built a platform for them in Python, Django, AWS, WordPress(Landing page)

## Web Developer /Infrastructure, 11/2019 to 01/2021 Big Oak Spa - Santiago, Chile

 Multiple ecommerce were made with WordPress and some plugins were edited, also NAS systems were installed in the office..

### **E**DUCATION

No Degree, Engineering in Computing And Informatics, 03/2018 Universidad Mayor - Santiago, Chile GPA:

High School Diploma, 12/2017 Colegio Santo Domingo - Santiago, Chile

#### **Personal Information**

RUN: 19.957.470-1 Birth Date: June 12, 1998 Nationality: Chilean

## **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

I'm a self taught Full Stack Developer, I've been learning programming languages since i was 14 years old and using Linux since then.

### CONTACT

Address: Nazarethkirchstraße 51, 13347 Berlin

**Phone:** (+56) 950128186

Email: joaquinsozag@gmail.com

## WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- joaquinsoza.dev
- linkedin.com/in/joaquinsoza/
- github.com/joaquinsoza

#### SKILLS

- Self-motivated professional
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- Programming Languages: Python, JavaScript, C#, Solidity, TypeScript
- Frameworks: React, Vue, Django
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, MariaDB
- Cloud: AWS, DigitalOcean
- Others: Docker, Node.js
- Advanced Linux user

#### CERTIFICATIONS

- Full Stack Engineer, Codecademy 2021
- Solidity/Blockchain, Dapp University 2021
- React, Codecademy 2020-2021
- HTML & CSS, Codecademy 2019

## LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native language

**English:** 

Advanced

C1